<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Updates xmlns="http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/libUpdate">
  <Latest version="2.1.0.0">
    <Name>WKD Web Comic Downloader v2.1</Name>
    <Description>
      This update replaces the tracking code to improve functionality
      and adds Endless Origami to the list of supported comics.
    </Description>
    <ChangeLog>
      - Updated tracking code to improve stability and functionality
      - Added Endless Origami to the list of supported comics
    </ChangeLog>
    <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/wkd/WKDSetup.exe</Download>
    <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/wkd/updates/2100</Info>
  </Latest>

  <Archive>
    <Update version="2.0.0.0">
      <Name>WKD Web Comic Downloader v2.0</Name>
      <Description>
        This update replaces much of Web Comic Downloader's
        user interface code with code that is faster and less
        CPU intensive when performing animations.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - User interface uses new animations code to reduce CPU
        usage when running animations
        - Update code has been revised to allow automatic updates
        to be performed.
        - XPath application has been updated to allow the user to
        enter the web address once the application has been launched.
        - Update code has been converted to use the same code used in
        NETKey for the sake of stability and performance.
        - Looking for Group added to the list of supported web comics
        - Added support for HTTP Cookies
        - Fixed Cyanide &amp; Happiness comic definition
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/wkd/WKDSetup.exe</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/wkd/updates/2000</Info>
    </Update>
    <Update version="1.8.0.0">
      <Name>WKD Web Comic Downloader v1.8</Name>
      <Description>
        Updates certain comic definitions to make use of the new
        Image Tags functionality.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Adds Image Tags functionality to add extra information to
        image files. This can include a name for the image and a
        description.
        - Adds the ability to force a comic to be saved in a specified
        image format. This is required due to the lack of EXIF tag support in
        PNG images.
        - Updates certain comic definitions to support this new functionality.
        - XKCD will now save the hover text in the image's description field.
        - Ctrl+Alt+Del will save the title of the comic in the image's title field.
        - Updates the web comic definition to allow new features to be controlled
        through web comic files.
        - Fixes a possible bug in the way file naming XPath expressions are calculated
        which could cause them to search for a "src" attribute if no attribute was
        found or specified.
        - File name XPaths and Image Tag XPaths will now handle &amp;#code; character
        codes correctly.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/wkd/WKD.7z</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/wkd/updates/1800</Info>
    </Update>
    <Update version="1.7.0.0">
      <Name>WKD Web Comic Downloader v1.7</Name>
      <Description>
        Fixes a problem on Windows XP where the dialog box which would
        appear if no web comic was selected would cause a crash.
        Also updates all the information dialog boxes to be more descriptive
        and improves error checking for web comic definitions.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Fixes a problem on Windows XP (and earlier) systems which
        would result in an error message being displayed to the
        user at launch if a new update was available.
        - Fixes a problem where if an XPath query in the naming scheme
        contained invalid file characters it would cause the download
        to stop.
        - Fixes a problem on Ctrl+Alt+Del where in some cases it would
        fail to download the main page. Now uses safe download code.
        - Updates all information dialog boxes to be more informative.
        - Application should no longer crash if a corrupt or invalid
        Web Comic Definition is supplied.
        - The application will now restart if it crashes after notifying
        the user.
        - Better scalability of message boxes based on OS version.
        - Prevents a crash caused by the wrong message box type being
        opened on Windows XP and earlier systems if no comic was selected
        and the download button was pressed.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/wkd/WKD_170.7z</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/wkd/updates/1700</Info>
    </Update>
    <Update version="1.6.0.0">
      <Name>WKD Web Comic Downloader v1.6</Name>
      <Description>
        Fixes a problem on Windows XP where the update available
        dialog would cause an error message to be displayed.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Fixes a problem on Windows XP (and earlier) systems which
        would result in an error message being displayed to the
        user at launch if a new update was available.
        - Changes the new update dialog to the standard Windows XP
        message box on Windows XP and lower systems to fix the
        above issue.
        - Adds error reporting code to the application to aid in the
        diagnosis of future problems.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/wkd/WKD_160.7z</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/wkd/updates/1600</Info>
    </Update>
    <Update version="1.5.0.0">
      <Name>WKD Web Comic Downloader v1.5</Name>
      <Description>
        Adds Pon &amp; Zi and SH*THOUSE to the comic list as well
        as fixing a bug which resulted in the last character of the
        image's extension replacing the last character in the image's
        name.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Fixed a problem in the relative link code which could result
        in a path which had a duplicate protocol prefix. This was caused
        when the application attempted to either get a parent path or
        the root path where the result was the passed parameter. This
        would cause the function to not remove the protocol from the
        begining resulting in a duplicate.
        - Added Pon &amp; Zi to the comic list
        - Fixed a possible problem with Head Trip by adding a LastComicAddress
        and explicitly telling it to download the comic on that last address.
        - Added SH*THOUSE to the comic list
        - Tested and confirmed that all relative path code functions correctly
        (Including ../)
        - Fixed an issue with generated file names resulting in the last character
        of the name being replaced with the last character of the file extension.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/wkd/WKD_150.7z</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/wkd/updates/1500</Info>
    </Update>
    <Update version="1.4.0.0">
      <Name>WKD Web Comic Downloader v1.4</Name>
      <Description>
        Fixes a few small problems with certain comics including
        XKCD as well as adding new features to the Comic Defintions
        specification.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Fixed a problem where comics that used &amp;gt; to represent
        &gt; would fail to match on XPath searches. (Temporary fix)
        - Fixed by adding an alternative search XPath which uses
        &amp;amp;gt; in the place of &amp;gt;
        - Added a "LastComicHandling" section to the advanced options
        in Comic Defintions allowing you to specify whether or not
        the application should download the image that appears on
        the page after the last comic link.
        For example:
        XKCD uses "#" as a placeholder for when you have reached
        the last comic. You would specify "true" for the
        "StopImmediately" attribute to prevent the application from
        downloading a duplicate image for the next page.
        - Added a "PageDownloadOptions" section to the advanced options
        in Comic Defintions allowing you to specify the code that should
        be used for downloading pages. Safe Code does not display the
        download progress for the page that is downloading but may be
        less likely to fail half way through downloading the page.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/wkd/WKD_140.7z</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/wkd/updates/1400</Info>
    </Update>
    <Update version="1.3.0.0">
      <Name>WKD Web Comic Downloader v1.3</Name>
      <Description>
        Fixes a few small problems with certain comics as well
        as implementing a new code system for handling relative
        links. Should now be able to handle ../../image.jpg without
        any problems.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - New relative link handling code which supports
        - "/" (Go to root)
        - "./" (Current Directory)
        - "../" (Current Directory's parent) [Recursive support]
        - Fix for VGCats
        - Removed Penny Arcade temporarily due to a problem downloading
        comics. Will be added again when this problem has been fixed.
        - Removed Questionable Content due to a problem downloading comics.
        Will be added again when this problem has been fixed.
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/wkd/WKD_130.7z</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/wkd/updates/1300</Info>
    </Update>
    <Update version="1.2.0.0">
      <Name>WKD Web Comic Downloader v1.2</Name>
      <Description>
        Fixes problems when servers time out as well as issues
        with links that had spaces in them.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Fix for Ctrl+Alt+Del where the application would not
        stop attempting to download the latest comic.
        (Fixed in definition file)
        - Fix for Cyanide and Happiness where servers would return
        a 404 Not Found error on some images due to the application
        not replacing spaces with %20.
        - Added rounded corners to certain UI elements for better
        flow
        - Added options for setting whether standby is disabled while
        downloading.
        - Added a settings page
        - Fixed a problem with comic pages which did not contain an image
        (Cyanide and Happiness often post youtube videos instead)
        - Fixed a problem where comics who's latest image appeared on
        the root comic page would result in the application never being
        able to update the comic. (May cause updates to download 2 current
        images before begining the update)
        - Completely new download code which should result in better stability
        and no longer relies on error catching (slow) to handle possible problems.
        - Fixed a problem with the Garfield Minus Garfield definition file
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/wkd/WKD.7z</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/wkd/updates/1200</Info>
    </Update>
    <Update version="1.1.0.0">
      <Name>WKD Web Comic Downloader v1.1</Name>
      <Description>
        ----Major Update----
        Fixes numerous issues with poorly formatted HTML in certain
        web pages. (Previous version only supported XHTML). Also adds
        a workaround for HotSPOT Anti-Hotlinking protection.
        Not to mention major functionality improvements and bug fixes.
        Comics downloaded using v1.0.0 will not work with this version.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - Fixes issues with poorly formatted HTML on pages
        - Adds a workaround for HotSPOT Anti-HotLinking which could prevent
        the application from downloading certain comics.
        - Fixes problems with the application not stopping the download
        of comics after the last page has been reached. May also reduce
        bandwidth usage by not reloading the last page.
        - Better UI responsiveness making use of new movement code.
        - Revised comic definition format
        - Allows you to specify naming patterns, XPaths for accquiring
        file names as well as custom referral values.
        - Will prevent your system from entering standby while downloading
        - Stores your comics folder and the last downloaded comic in a settings
        file for future use. This makes selecting comics (after initial setup)
        considerably faster.
        - New UI Layout for better aesthetics
        - Remaining time estimate now functions correctly.
        - Includes many more comic definition files
        - Chainsaw Suit
        - Ctrl+Alt+Del
        - Cyanide and Happiness
        - Garfield minus Garfield
        - Girl Genius
        - Head Trip
        - Penny Arcade
        - Questionable Content
        - Sequential Art
        - VG Cats
        - XKCD
        - Adds update checking code (Will not automatically update
        application files like ArmA 2 Mod Launcher)
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/wkd/WKD_110.7z</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/wkd/updates/1100</Info>
    </Update>
    <Update version="1.0.0.0">
      <Name>WKD Web Comic Downloader v1.0</Name>
      <Description>
        This application allows you to download large numbers of
        web comics easily to your computer.
        Unlike other applications this one makes use of XPath
        expressions to locate the images which allows it to function
        with web comics that do not name their images sequentially.
      </Description>
      <ChangeLog>
        - No changes
      </ChangeLog>
      <Download>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/downloads/wkd/WKD_100.7z</Download>
      <Info>http://www.sierrasoftworks.com/wkd</Info>
    </Update>
  </Archive>
</Updates>